So, today...
We're going to play a game!
Wow!
Aki-chan, you play a lot of smartphone
games.
I do.
What are we going to play?
Amoasu.
We're going to play a game called
Aki-chan, you play a lot of games.
I do.
I played a lot of games.
This game is a little bit difficult.
There is a character called Imposter.
The player kills the imposter during
the game.
But, you can't kill the imposter.
If you kill a lot of imposters, you
win.
If you win, you can clear the mission.
If you clear the mission, you win.
I see.
It's fun to play with a lot of people.
We're going to play this game with the
staff of VTuber, VTuber, and VTuber's
bus guide.
This program is a program where members
who are active to promote something
exciting
to the public,機會をくれる。
Thank you for watching!
Let's try it.
I've never seen that before.
When is he going home today...
Thank you for watching!
I see.
It's quiet.
Ah!
Was it over the other side?
yeah aper
Thank you for watching.
I got it.
The staff who bought the egg-baked one
came out from the next room.
I see.
So, I was doing my job.
Were you doing your job?
Because I'm the culprit.
I saw you coming out from the next
room.
So, I'm saying that.
No, no.
You were making a voice.
I thought you were killed.
I thought you were dead.
I was alive.
I see.
Which one is the culprit?
There are several times.
If you kill me and the staff, you can
win.
To be continued.
What were you doing?
I was working in the electrical room.
I was in the electrical room, too.
Aki-chan came out of the air
conditioner and I saw her.
Wait, which one?
We passed each other.
We passed each other at the gas
station.
Then, we went to the electrical room
and came out.
Please subscribe to this channel.
safely
The winner is...
Great!
Isn't it cool?
It's like a squadron.
It's a ghost.
It was killed right away.
Isn't it cute?
Let's do it again.
It's fun.
I don't want to be killed again.
I think it will be far away if I get
closer.
I'm always like this.
It's like a red light.
That's an impostor.
It's like a human being's special
skill.
It reduces oxygen in a place or closes
a door.
So I'm going to get rid of it.
Let's do it again.
The crew won.
The impostor lost.
Let's do it again.
Hmm
What is this button?
If you do that, you can do Kai at once.
Hi.
Maybe we should fill in the green area
with the tasks we completed.
Oh, yes. The upper one.
Is that so?
We should fill in the green area with
the tasks we completed.
Oh, yes. The upper one.
Is that so?
Maybe we should fill in the green area
with the tasks we completed.
I'm glad I was able to help you.
When I'm doing tasks, I get killed.
I understand.
I get killed.
Use the eavesdropping to find as many
kills as you can.
I'm scared.
What?
Three people died.
I'm scared.
I didn't do anything when I passed by
Aki-chan.
Thank you for watching.
What did you do?
I was in the electric room.
Because it was shining.
I was there.
I did two things.
Where?
Where was it?
There.
One was a Wi-Fi mark.
The other was...
I did it.
Wait.
We were together for a long time.
You mean you can't talk with us?
I know.
Wait, you are not me.
I'm Sae.
What were you doing?
I worked extra hard.
I did it twice.
I couldn't use the game console.
You know, the place where you sit down
to play games.
I could use it until a while ago, but I
couldn't use it.
This time?
Yes.
I did it with a stick.
I stuck a stick in my mouth like this.
I did it for 1 second.
I'm sorry.
No.
Yay!
I'm scared.
I killed her.
Why did you kill her?
I thought something was coming.
I heard a funny voice.
This is funny.
Let's go to the third floor.
Let's go.
Who's going to start?
I'm going to clear the mission.
I'm going to start.
This is the first time I'm seeing this.
Even though I made the inconsistent
progress, it matchluss under still that
blocking we were seeing only in fantasy.
This spot is difficult.
I'm sorry.
First of all, as an area capture
You hold Bayo like this
Then you press the main key
Luor G, G, G, G
Let's start with first
Then this
Unfortunately, I usually slow the game
down
I see.
I'm sorry.
Ah!
I got it.
When we were cut off from the oxygen,
the staff, bus guide and I went to the
oxygen room.
Aki was there too.
We were on the roof.
Kaname was definitely a crew member.
But the bus guide said she had played
this game before.
So you went to the oxygen room?
Just the choreography?
But you can do that in Kaido.
You can?
I see.
But you cleared the mission?
Yes, we did.
You did it in Kaido, right?
It was like that.
I wonder which one.
What about you, Helsinko?
I did the scan.
What was that?
I don't know.
Did you do the scan?
I wonder which one.
I was wrong once.
You were wrong once.
Please watch again.
Which one? I'm scared.
I don't know.
It's possible.
I'm scared.
Yay!
We did it!
I didn't think it would work.
I thought you were going to kill me.
But you were so nice.
I was going to say, let's stay
together.
You were so nice.
I was so surprised.
I thought you were going to kill me.
And then my mom killed me.
I said I was doing a mission.
I was killed while I was doing a
mission.
That's why I said, let's stay together.
I was doing a mission.
I thought, stop it.
Let's do it again.
Let's do the last one.
Let's do it.
It's started.
There are some things that you can't
use in the mission.
The location has changed.
I can't use the Wi-Fi.
Speeds up when found
The mission isn't there?
Yellow...
I'll go.
Are you doing the mission?
I'm doing it.
I'm done.
What's this?
Ah! I'm being reported! Someone report
me!
Eh? Why are you being reported?
I love you.
There are many.
How do I do this?
Do I just push this?
If you don't push it, it will change.
I pushed it.
Oh!
This?
Yes!
Yes.
I think it's Hitoga.
No, no.
It's like...
The person who's gone is gone.
Hitoga was taken away.
But I...
I thought Hitoga was killed.
Wait.
I...
When I was with Karamin...
Oh, yeah.
You didn't kill her.
I thought Hitoga was the first one.
But it's not.
Wait, I cleared the mission.
I was with everyone.
But I didn't kill Hitoga.
So I thought Hitoga was the last one.
But I thought I didn't kill her.
Wait, wait, wait.
I did something.
I did the moving one.
The moving one?
I cleared the mission.
What?
How was it?
Kaho was dead, too.
Oh, yeah.
I didn't meet them.
The bus guide...
I didn't meet the bus guide.
5 seconds left.
Hurry up.
Hitoga.
No.
Thank you for watching.
At best, the blood the winner will give
is akira.
What will go to the bitter end of
fighting?
So the plank that connects theUTU
RALLIES?
The color is similar, so it's like
KALAXY
Because it connects the love
When the loss isutive, the death coming
Ah So basically it always happen
I was there all the time.
I was wondering what she was doing.
I see.
Did you say,
I'm doing it?
Yes.
I was like, yes, I'm doing it.
I see.
I was like that.
It was fun.
I want to do it again.
We can do it online.
Let's do it again.
Next time, with Oharu.
Oharu, I don't know.
It was fun to do this for the first
time.
We will do it again.
See you next week.
I'm Naito Naito.
I'm back with my father's pension.
Normal!
Meeting a genius boy who has changed
him.
What are you doing here?
I'm making a game here.
A game?
This is an invitation from a creator.
A creator?
A legendary game creator.
A creator.
At first glance, it's just a normal
middle school student and a detective's
adventure story.
What is this mark?
I'll try it.
To a creator.
What?
I'm going home.
Wow!
Master Soya, please behave yourself.
I'm just a kid after all.
Can they clear the game?
Watch out, Soya!
Tom & Soya in Our Fortress
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for
yesterday
The city after the rain is colored
Draw a piece of the future on the
canvas of my damaged heart
Don't blur my sight
I can say it now, the reason for my
tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city lights after the rain are
sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the rain drops
I wear a rainbow dress